正确答案是android.permission.INTERNET  小朋友们猜对了么
The answer is android.permission.INTERNET. I'll show you now,
我来告诉你应该把这个权限添加到哪里
where it's located in the code. Under the
在main文件夹下  打开AndroidManifest.xml这个文件
main folder open up the AndroidManifest.xml file.
看一下这个文件  我们在中
Within the Android manifest file, we declare uses
通过设置权限名字的方式来声明权限
permission, with the name of the permission. We
我们要使用verbose级别的日志把返回的
verified that the data returned is correct by
JSON字符串打印出来  以此确认返回
adding a verbose log statement for printing out
的数据是正确的  日志的打印语句是在FetchWeatherTask类中的
the Forecast JSON String. This is in the FetchWeatherTask.
我们可以验证一下加的日志是会正确输出的  这次我要用
We can verify that it's going to show up in the logs. For this example, I'm
命令行的方式  这都是实时的日志  如果我点击了刷新按钮
going to use the command line. These are the real time logs, and then if I
我就能在这里看到天气数据了  这是日志输出级别verbose  这是
hit refresh, then I see the weather data here. The verbose log, and this is our
我们为那个类设置的日志标识符FetchWeatherTask  这是Forecast JSON String的内容
log tag FetchWeatherTask. Here's the Forecast JSON String,
这串 JSON 字符串是从服务器上返回的所有数据
and this is all the output from the server.